http://www.clubstaffing.com/terms-of-use/

ClubStaffing
Call or Apply Now!
Crisis Jobs
Apply Now!
HomeTerms of Use
We are delighted that you’ve decided to use the services that Club Staffing offers on our site and we hope that you find it to be a great experience. For both your protection and ours, we have established the following terms of use which we expect all our visitors, whether registered or not, to follow while on our site. Your continued use of our site means that you acknowledge these terms of use and agree to abide by them at all times. Because we reserve the right to modify these terms of use at any time without notice to you, please check them regularly. Please note that you will be referred to as "user" from time to time in this agreement.
General Rules
You agree and continue to agree to use our Web site in a manner consistent with all applicable laws and regulations and in accordance with the terms and conditions set out in the policies and guidelines outlined below.
Registration Obligations
In consideration of your use of the site, you agree to provide true, accurate, current and complete information about yourself as prompted by the site's registration. If you provide any information that is untrue, inaccurate, not current or incomplete, or we have reasonable grounds to suspect that such information is untrue, inaccurate, not current or incomplete, we have the right to refuse you any and all current or future use of the site. Please note that our site is not intended for the use of children. We have assumed that the users of our site are over the age of 18. If you are under the age of 18, you must obtain your parents' permission prior to using our site.
Privacy Policy
Registration data and certain other information about you is subject to our privacy policy. For more information, see our privacy policy.
Rules of Conduct for Use of the Blog
We do not control the information posted in the comments of our blog and do not guarantee the accuracy, integrity or quality of such content. You understand that by using this blog you may be exposed to content that is offensive or objectionable. You agree that you bear all risks associated with the use of any content, including any reliance on the accuracy, completeness or usefulness of such content. Under no circumstances will we be liable in any way for any content, including, but not limited to any errors or omissions in any content, any loss or damage of any kind incurred as a result of the use of any content posted, e-mailed or otherwise transmitted via the blog comments. Certain behaviors will not be tolerated on our site, and by continuing to use our site, you are agreeing that you will not post any of the following material:
Advertising or any form of commercial solicitation.
Material which is untrue or which defames, abuses, harasses or threatens others.
Statements that are bigoted, hateful, mean- spirited, or ethnically or racially offensive.
Material that advocates illegal activity or discusses illegal activities with the intent to commit them.
Unauthorized copyrighted material, including, but not limited to, text, sound or graphic files.
Material that contains vulgar, obscene, pornographic, or indecent language or images.
You acknowledge that any posted content solely represents the views of the user who posted it and does not represent the views of or a validation by Club Staffing. We shall have the right, but not the obligation, in our sole discretion to refuse or remove any content that violates the above terms or is otherwise objectionable. Any user who posts objectionable material on our site will be responsible for all of our damages arising from such posting. In addition, depending on the nature and extent of the violation, we may, at our sole discretion terminate such user's account.
Links
Our site provides links to third party Web sites. Because we have no control over such third party sites, you acknowledge and agree that we are not responsible for the availability of such external sites or resources, and do not endorse and are not responsible or liable for any content, advertising, products, or other materials on or available from such sites or resources. You further acknowledge and agree that we are not responsible or liable, directly or indirectly, for any damage or loss caused or alleged to be caused by or in connection with your use of or reliance on any such content, goods or services available on or through any such site.
License to Use Our Site
We grant you a personal, non-exclusive, non-assignable and non-transferable license to use and display the contents of and services on our site. Unauthorized copying or duplication of the contents in any manner including software that has been modified, merged or included on the site, or the written materials associated therewith is expressly forbidden. You acknowledge that you may not sublicense, transfer, sell or assign this license or the services received thereunder. Any attempt to sublicense, transfer, sell or assign this license is void.
Unauthorized access to registered areas of the site by non-registered users is prohibited.
Posting of Copyrighted or Indecent Materials
Any posting of the following material is strictly prohibited:
Unauthorized copies of or links to any unauthorized use of copyrighted photographs, drawings, graphics, text or other writings, computer programs or other software, recordings or designs; files containing advertisements or solicitations aimed at persuading other members to use certain goods or services; any material or links to material of a sexually explicit nature, including photographs and text.
Copyrighted material, including without limitation text, photographs, sound, video and music, may not be placed on the site without the express permission of the author or owner of the copyright on the material. You acknowledge that only the owner or someone authorized by the owner to post the material may do so. The downloading of copyrighted material is allowed by you but only for your own personal use. You may not copy, reproduce, retransmit, distribute, publish, commercially exploit or otherwise transfer any copyrighted material. The burden of determining that any information, software or any other content on the site is not protected by copyright rests with you. You acknowledge that we and third party content providers remain the owners of the posted materials, and that you do not acquire any of those ownership rights by downloading or posting copyrighted materials. If you have questions about permissions issues, please email us.
Limitation of Liability and Warranty
YOU AGREE THAT USE OF OUR SITE IS ENTIRELY AT YOUR OWN RISK. OUR SITE AND THE SERVICES PROVIDED THEREIN ARE PROVIDED "AS IS," WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EITHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION ANY WARRANTY FOR INFORMATION, SERVICES, UNINTERRUPTED ACCESS, OR PRODUCTS PROVIDED THROUGH OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SERVICE, INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION OUR SOFTWARE OR SERVICES LICENSED TO YOU AND THE RESULTS OBTAINED THROUGH THE SERVICE (UNLESS SUCH WARRANTIES ARE LEGALLY INCAPABLE OF EXCLUSION). SPECIFICALLY, WE DISCLAIM ANY AND ALL WARRANTIES, INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION: 1) ANY WARRANTIES CONCERNING THE AVAILABILITY, ACCURACY OR CONTENT OF INFORMATION, PRODUCTS OR SERVICES; AND 2) ANY WARRANTIES OF TITLE OR WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY OR FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.
THIS DISCLAIMER OF LIABILITY APPLIES TO ANY DAMAGES OR INJURY CAUSED BY ANY FAILURE OF PERFORMANCE, ERROR, OMISSION, INTERRUPTION, DELETION, DEFECT, DELAY INOPERATION OR TRANSMISSION, COMPUTER VIRUS, COMMUNICATION LINE FAILURE, THEFT OR DESTRUCTION OR UNAUTHORIZED ACCESS TO, ALTERATION OF, OR USE OF RECORD, WHETHER FOR BREACH OF CONTRACT, TORTIOUS BEHAVIOR, NEGLIGENCE, OR UNDER ANY OTHER CAUSE OF ACTION. YOU SPECIFICALLY ACKNOWLEDGE THAT WE ARE NOT LIABLE FOR THE DEFAMATORY, OFFENSIVE OR ILLEGAL CONDUCT OF OTHER USERS OR THIRD-PARTIES AND THAT THE RISK OF INJURY FROM THE FOREGOING RESTS ENTIRELY WITH YOU.
OUR ENTIRE LIABILITY AND YOUR EXCLUSIVE REMEDY WITH RESPECT TO THE USE OF OUR SERVICES IS THE CANCELLATION OF YOUR REGISTRATION WITH US.
NEITHER WE NOR ANY OF OUR AGENTS, AFFILIATES, CO-BRANDERS, PARTNERS OR CONTENT PROVIDERS SHALL BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT OR INCIDENTAL DAMAGES, LOST PROFITS, OR SPECIAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES ARISING OUT OF USE OF THE SITE OR INABILITY TO GAIN ACCESS TO OR USE THE SITE OR OUT OF ANY BREACH OF ANY WARRANTY. YOU HEREBY ACKNOWLEDGE THAT THE PROVISIONS OF THIS SECTION SHALL APPLY TO ALL CONTENT AND SERVICES ON THE SITE.
Service Marks and Trademarks
Club Staffing is a registered mark of AMN Healthcare, Inc. Any other service marks or trademarks appearing on the site are service marks or trademarks of their respective owners. You shall not display, disparage, dilute, or taint our service mark or use any confusingly similar marks or use our mark in such a way that would misrepresent who the proper owner of such marks is. Any permitted use of our service mark by you shall inure to our benefit.
Indemnification
Upon our request, you agree to defend, indemnify and hold us harmless from any dispute which may arise from your breach of the terms of this agreement. You agree to hold us and our affiliates, employees, contractors, officers, directors, co-branders, partners and content providers harmless from any and all claims and expenses, including attorney's fees and court costs, related to your violation of this agreement, including the rules of conduct, or any information, software, files, messages or other content placed on our site by you. We reserve the right, at our own expense, to assume the exclusive defense and control of any matter otherwise subject to indemnification by you. In that event, you shall have no further obligation to provide indemnification to us in that matter.
Termination of Service
You may terminate your right to use our site and services at any time by notification to us as set forth above. We may terminate your account or access rights to the site at any time, without notice, for conduct that we believe violates this agreement or other policies or guidelines that we have posted on our site.
Your Acceptance of These Terms
By using this site, you signify your assent to the Club Staffing terms of use and privacy policy. If you do not agree with these terms and our privacy policy, please refrain from using our site. Your continued use of the Club Staffing site following a reasonable notice of changes to our privacy policy or terms of use will mean you accept the changes.
Last updated: April 1, 2011
©
2017 AMN Healthcare, Inc. All rights reserved. Reproduction and distribution of
these materials is prohibited without the expressed written authorization of
AMN Healthcare, Inc.
